Sebastian Paulo Haloho

Yogyakarta, Indonesia | bastianhaloho12@gmail.com | +6288228655310 | LinkedIn | GitHub

Summary

I graduated in information systems at a university in Yogyakarta. I have understanding and experience to develop websites using HTML, Javascript, CSS, PHP and MySQL programming from my lectures. I also have understanding of mobile application development with React Native, Node JS, and React JS tools from the bootcamp program that I am currently participating. I am very interested to have a career in technology, especially in the field of application development. However, I am also open to career opportunities in other fields that suit my abilities.

Skill

HTML, Javascript, PHP, MySql, React Native, React.Js, Node.Js, Communation, Team work, Problem solving, Critical thinking, UX.

Education

CodeMasters Bootcamp Program

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

Full Stack Development

- Study and explore front end mobile development material using the React Native framework, back end development material using Node JS with Express JS, and deepen website development material using React JS.
- Create a mobile application project as a final project in React Native material by forming a development team.
- Final project for back end engineer material using Express JS and several other tools. Work to form a team and
 create structured data according to application needs. Create an API that can be used for applications with an
 appropriate structure

Final project

- <u>Toyota Trust Mobile App</u>: Building a mobile application for selling and trading cars from the supervisor's side
 using the React Native framework which aims to be the final project in React Native material at the bootcamp at
 Codemasters.
- <u>Healty Foods</u>: Building an API and database flow from the backend side for a healthy food sales application as a task of understanding the back end engineer.

Universitas Teknologi Yogyakarta

Sep 2017 - Oct 2022

Information System

- Learn about the workflow that exists in the system with information that has value. Develop an application that contains an information system with a clear structure and can be implemented in business.
- Understanding and experience to develop websites using HTML, Javascript, CSS, PHP and MySQL programming.

Thesis

Monjali Petshop Web: The final project in college is to create a sales website for a pet shop which can be
implemented with a workflow that is in line with company sales from creating data structures to creating webbased applications.

Experience

PT. Medika Digital Nusantara

Jul 2023 - Sep 2023

Freelance Customer Service (Technical)

- Responding to client queries in a timely and accurate way, via phone, email or chat.
- Identifying client needs and helping customers use specific features.
- Communicate with the development team to improve and update the features that clients want.
- Update our internal databases with information about technical issues and useful discussions with clients.
- Follow up with clients to ensure their technical issues are resolved.

Raja Tas Batam Apr 2020 – Jun 2021

Part-time Reseller

- Selling goods on social media sites or platforms and online shops.
- Serving sales of goods to customers.